I Am Bruce Lee is a documentary film directed by Pete McCormack.
Bruce Lee is universally recognized as the pioneer who elevated martial arts in film to an art form, and this
documentary will reveal why Bruce Lee's flame burns brighter now than the day he died over three decades ago.
The greatest martial artists, athletes, actors, directors, and producers in the entertainment
business today will share their feelings about the one who started it all.
We will interview the people whose lives, careers, and belief systems were
forever altered by the legendary "Father of Martial Arts Cinema".
Rarely seen archival footage and classic photos will
punctuate the personal testimonials.
Prepare to be inspired.
Self (archival), played by Bruce Lee.
Self, played by Linda Lee Cadwell.
Self, played by Shannon Lee.
Self / 3rd Floor Guardian / Pasqual, played by Dan Inosanto.
Self, played by Diana Lee Inosanto.
Self, played by Kobe Bryant.
I Am Bruce Lee is a 2012 American documentary film
directed and written by Pete McCormack.
The film documents the life of Bruce Lee, the famous actor and martial artist,
featuring interviews with his widow Linda Emery, and daughter, Shannon Lee.
It won a Leo Award in 2012.
The film explores themes of martial arts, biography, martial
arts master, martial artist, east asian lead.